export const flashCard = {
    family: [{
        front: 'Parent',
        back: 'cha; bố; mẹ',
        exampleList: [
            "I'm going to meet Richard's parents for the first time this weekend.",
            "One of the joys of being a parent is watching the child's character develop.",
            "As a parent you try to create a stable home environment for your children to grow up in."
        ]
    }, {
        front: 'Father',
        back: 'cha, bố',
        exampleList: [
            "My father took me to watch the football every Saturday.",
            "The children's father came to pick them up from school.",
            "Are you giving a sermon, Father?"
        ]
    }, {
        front: 'Sibling',
        back: 'anh ruột; chị ruột; em ruột',
        exampleList: [
            "I have four siblings: three brothers and a sister.",
            "There was great sibling rivalry (= competition) between Peter and his brother.",
        ]
    }, {
        front: 'Husband',
        back: 'chồng',
        exampleList: [
            "I've never met Fiona's husband.",
            "She confessed to her husband that she had sold her wedding ring.",
            "My main aim in life is to be a good husband and father."
        ]
    }, {
        front: 'Grandmother',
        back: 'bà',
        exampleList: [
            "Both my grandmothers were from Scotland.",
            "The apple pie was as good as the one my grandmother used to make.",
            "My grandmother was booked for speeding last week."
        ]
    }],
    animal: [{
        front: 'Frog(n)',
        back: 'con ếch',
        exampleList: [
            "Are there any species of frog indigenous to the area?",
            "The witch put a magic spell on the prince and turned him into a frog.",
            "We had to dissect a worm and a frog in our biology practical today."
        ]
    }, {
        front: 'Poach(v)',
        back: 'câu trộm, săn trộm',
        exampleList: [
            "We had poached eggs for breakfast.",
            "Do you like pears poached in red wine?",
            "The farmer claimed that he shot the men because they were poaching on his land."
        ]
    }, {
        front: 'Shrinking(adj)',
        back: 'nhỏ dần, thu hẹp dần',
        exampleList: [
            "I’m worried about washing that shirt in case it shrinks.",
            "The shrinking workforce would have to support a growing number of retired people.",
            "a shrinking budget/economy/market"
        ]
    }],
    travel: [{
        front: 'Journey(n)',
        back: 'cuộc hành trình',
        exampleList: [
            "I love going on long journeys.",
            "Have a safe journey!",
            "Did you have a good journey?"
        ]
    }, {
        front: 'Carpooling(n)',
        back: 'hình thức đi chung xe',
        exampleList: [
            "Carpooling saves on travel expenses.",
            "We share carpooling duties.",
        ]
    }]
}